# Ayaka Miyake

Condon, UK ☐ +44 7709-211-613 ☐ ayakamiyake7@gmail.com ☐ https://www.linkedin.com/in/ayaka-miyake/
(a) https://github.com/ayakamiyake7 ☐ https://portfolio-ayakamiyake7.vercel.app/

### About

Enthusiastic Front End Developer with skills in developing component-based responsive web applications using React, Next.js, and Javascript. I also worked in Web Design as a web designer. I enjoy working with React.js. I am also passionate about design and using that in my components and successfully involved in both the front end and the design process with UI/UX.

#### Skills

React / Recoil / Next.js / TypeScript / JavaScript / jQuery / HTML / CSS / SASS / Version Control / Web design / Figma / Adobe XD

## Experience

Freelance Front End Developer - Argo, Inc. Remote Contract | 08. 2021 - Present

- · Helped clients develop services that were specific to their needs.
- Instrumental in a team of 2 developers, reviewed code and helped provide additional perspective on the board process.
- · Created 3 landing pages in a week whlist organising the design process / SCSS single-handedly.

Front End Developer - Argo, Inc. Nagoya, Japan I 04. 2019 – 09. 2020

- Tasked with the maintenance and updates to 10+ websites and provided person centred care to those clients.
- Took verbal instructions from clients and turned into design components such as contact form and buttons with 2 team members and satisfied clients with the outcome.
- · Developed frontend using JavaScript collaborating with backend teams to deliver projects.

Web Designer - Piece Craft, Inc. Nagoya, Japan I 04. 2018 – 03. 2019

- Re-designed the website to increase user engagement for the product and increased products purchases by 20% through the website.
- · Developed front-end using JavaScript with revised brand guidelines to reflect the new brand image with help of the team.
- · Collaborated with both clients and back-end teams to convert client specifications to fully functional products.

Civil Servant - Sekigahara Town Hall Gifu, Japan I 04. 2014 – 03. 2018

- Designed the layout of the town's monthly magazines to attract more readers.
- Increased dramatically profits in my area of responsibility by more than sixfold through my actions and implemented business system.

# **Projects**

Flat Review App 2022 - Present

- Built a web app with a backend developer for expatriates in London to find flats' reviews and comments.
- Used Next.js to update instantly the list interface without reloading.

https://github.com/ayakamiyake7/apartment\_for\_rent\_service

### Education

London College of Communication, UAL Online, London I 2020 - 2021

• Pre-degree, Certificate in Higher Education: Preparation for Design, Media and Screen

Human Academy Nagoya, Japan I 2016 - 2017

· Practice Web Design Course

Kwansei Gakuin University Hyogo, Japan I 2010 - 2014

• Undergraduate Degree in Policy Studies focusing on Urban Planning and Regional Revitalisation